http://www.massint.co.uk/general/privacy-policy.php

GDMS
Glow Discharge MSGD90 TraceApplicationsTime Resolved Analysis
KEMS
Knudsen Effusion MSApplications
AutoConcept
AutoConcept MSStandardApplicationsEnvironmentalApplicationsPetroleumApplications
ServiceDownloadsContact
Meeting the needs of our customers in providing the best products backed with comprehensive after-sales support and service.
TAKING MASS SPECTROMETRY TO THE NEXT LEVEL
Privacy Policy
Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited Respects Your Privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited. You can enquire from Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited as to what personal information was collected and you can request to have any collected personal information deleted.
Credit Card Details
The Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited website will never ask for credit card details.
External Sites
Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser to allow a site to recognize you each time you visit the site for customisation purposes etc. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information. Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited uses cookies where essential for correct operation of the site and to track visits to the site. The information collected is used to improve and monitor the use of the website and is not used in any way  to identify individuals. Cookies may also be used by other sites that link to or from this site.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Mass Spectrometry Instruments Limited have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
Follow us
Privacy Policy Terms of Use Site Map Contact
About Us
About UsHow To Find Us
GDMS
Glow Discharge MSGD90 TraceApplicationsTime Resolved Analysis
KEMS
Knudsen Effusion MSApplications
AutoConcept
AutoConcept MSStandardApplicationsEnvironmentalApplicationsPetroleumApplications
This site uses cookies for tracking and statistical purposes. Please read our privacy policy for more information.
Don't show this again
